So Dan, unfortunately Icky late in the
season went down with an injury. So
instantly one of our biggest strengths
of our football team, the offensive line
became a a area of need, a position of
need. And you went out and you resign,
you signed Rasheed Walker.
>> What about Rasheed Walker? I mean, we
had the opportunity to play against him
last year, but what about him as you
look at your free agency board? did you
identify
in him? What does he bring to the table?
>> So, he was one of the top tackles, you
know, in in free agency and honestly, I
didn't think there was a shot in the
hell that we were ever going to be able
to get him. But again, it's about our
pro staff did such a good job of staying
in contact with the agent and like he,
you know, his market kind of fell out a
little bit, which at times like, you
know, that's why you have to stay in it
because, you know, it's there's
unexpected things that happen. And when
he showed interest in us and coming here
and us potentially getting on on a
one-year deal, he knew the opportunity
was really good for him to come in. He
knew Icky was hurt. Um so we capitalized
on it. Um he's big, he's long. Um he's
good in pass protection. Uh some of the
run game stuff he has to improve. He
knows that too.
>> Um but this is like a big long athletic
guy. These guys are hard to find as we
all know. I mean these guys they don't
grow on trees. And for us to get him on
a one-year deal given our situation, I
mean it's it's huge for us.
>> Perfect. I mean, it just show us exactly
what he brings to the table, though. Let
let our fan base see what he's capable
of doing. Everybody loves this play
right here.
>> Yeah. So, he he's a tough dude now. He's
rough around the edges. Um there's no
nonsense to this guy.
>> Um as you see right here, like he's just
a physical dude. He's confident.
>> Um which is what you need out of left
tackle. You're going against some of the
best edge rushers on a week- toeek
basis. And this guy has experience and
he's tough. He's big and he's long. So,
he brings a lot to the table.
>> So, a lot of times you see guys that are
really big. A lot of times you and we've
played against guys like this,
>> they don't play like they look,
>> right?
>> Like they're not as physical as they
look. But you're telling me that this
guy plays the game
>> based on his size and athleticism. Like
he gets after it, right?
>> Yeah. He'll get after it now. And again,
like I said, there's some things. Yeah.
Does he have to improve the running on?
Yeah. Like some of the sustain and the
and the finish. Um but nobody's, you
know, a finished product, you know, and
he's still a young guy. He's 26 years
old.
>> That's why he signed with us so we can
help him get better, though. So, we
understand.
>> And we have some of the best O line
coaches in the league in my opinion. So,
I think he's going to come here. Um,
again, a guy that's played a lot of
football against a lot of high level
competition and big games and has
performed really well. So, it was a huge
get for us
>> and an unexpected one.
>> Definitely. So, as we watch him on this,
you get to see the athleticism, right?
You you get to see a guy do do his job
at the line of scrimmage, but still be
able to climb up to the next level, get
hands on linebacker. That's when you see
those explosive plays coming from your
running backs.
>> For sure. even here like pulling out on
the perimeter, you know, he makes it
look easy right here. And you know,
that's not easy for a 300 plus pound guy
to get out on the perimeter and and
execute a block on a more athletic DB or
linebacker. And you know, he shows he
can do it right here.
>> Yep. You get to see the athleticism
staying and finishing.
>> Yeah, finishing.
That's what I love about that play,
seeing this dude finish, not just
letting the guy stay up, be able to
still Yeah. get involved in the task,
>> setting the tone.
>> Thing that's great about him is like the
way he gets out of his stance and, you
know, technique-wise, he's got the
length, you know, you see him using his
hands right here.
>> Um, you know, again, like there's some
of the things he has to clean up in
terms of finish, but all the tools are
there. And, you know, I'd be shocked if
he didn't get better. If you go back
real quick, one of the things that I
love on this play, you don't see him
overextend. A lot of times in that
position,
>> you see guys get disconnected once the
defender make their make their second
move.
>> But he stays connected because he's
being patient on this particular play.
He never
>> he never seems like he's playing in a
hurry, right? On this play, I'm not
going to say never, but on this play, he
doesn't seem like he's playing in a
hurry. He's being patient. He
understands that this is a longer
developing route downfield for his
receivers.
>> So understanding I can't just overreact
to what's being shown. So I love the
patience from him on this play.
>> Yeah. And and for a big man like that to
have the feet and the athleticism to
mirror the guy and stay in front of him
and use his hands again like it's hard
finding these big athletic left tackles.
>> You did it though.
Appreciate it.
>> Let us see it.
>> It's another example.
>> Another example of him being patient.
Watch the late hands.
>> Using his length,
>> upfield hand, shocking
>> just staying active.
>> Yeah. One of the things the defenders is
waiting on for him to put those hands
out so he can slap them down. He just
continued to stay patient.
>> Yeah. And this is an athletic edge
rusher right here. You know, he knows
what he's going up against.
>> Absolutely.
>> You got to stay patient against those
guys, take good angles coming out of
your set, and
>> all the tools are there for him to just
like keep growing and and turn into a
really good one.
>> I love to see two different teams
playing with both of our players on
those teams. That's crazy.
>> Got to scout both guys on this
particular play. How many times did you
get to watch them go against each other
>> being Yeah, they went against each other
a few times. Um, again, they they both
uh held their own at different points.
So,
>> love it. Love it. And again, man, you
know, we just love to see when you go
out and you find these gems for us.